<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on News English</title>
    <link>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on News English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dunhuang Dance Troupe of Northwest University for Nationalities inaugurated</title>
      <link>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/dunhuang-dance-troupe-of-northwest-university-for-nationalities-inaugurated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/dunhuang-dance-troupe-of-northwest-university-for-nationalities-inaugurated/</guid>
      <description>New Gansu
&amp;ldquo;Dunhuang Dance Troupe of Northwest University for Nationalities was inaugurated.
New Gansu Client Lanzhou (New Gansu - Gansu Daily reporter Su Jiaying) November 29 to 30, the Northwest University for Nationalities hosted an international academic conference held in Lanzhou. At the opening ceremony of the conference, the &amp;ldquo;Dunhuang Dance Troupe of Northwest University for Nationalities&amp;rdquo; was inaugurated.
The conference centered on dance scientific research, dance culture research, dance education research, and other aspects of communication and interaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interviews | Gala Crew: The Light Behind the Stage, Belongs to Them</title>
      <link>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/interviews-gala-crew-the-light-behind-the-stage-belongs-to-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/interviews-gala-crew-the-light-behind-the-stage-belongs-to-them/</guid>
      <description>The light behind the stage belongs to them. November 25
Summary Preparation, stage walking, light pairing, hyping, venue discipline &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; Behind every glittering party, there is always a group of silent staff. They are the planners, the directors, the hosts, the persons in charge of the venue discipline, the guardians of the evening party, and the hermits who are busy in the corner of the performance site. The light in front of the stage belongs to the actors, and the light behind the stage belongs to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interviews | Hardworking Teachers in the Pomegranate Seed Cup</title>
      <link>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/interviews-hardworking-teachers-in-the-pomegranate-seed-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/interviews-hardworking-teachers-in-the-pomegranate-seed-cup/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The second &amp;ldquo;Pomegranate Seed Cup&amp;rdquo; Campus Dance Competition was held in the Basketball Hall of the Yuzhong Campus of Northwest University for Nationalities. The theme of the event was &amp;ldquo;Youthful Heart to the Party, Dance Art to China&amp;rdquo;, which was jointly organized by the Student Work Department (Department), Youth League Committee, and Dance College of Northwest University for Nationalities. In the interval of the activity, we interviewed the teachers in charge of this activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interviews | Performers at the Pomegranate Seed Cup</title>
      <link>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/interviews-performers-at-the-pomegranate-seed-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/interviews-performers-at-the-pomegranate-seed-cup/</guid>
      <description>Dance is a language hidden in the soul, and dance is like realizing a dream with one&amp;rsquo;s posture. In the Award Ceremony of the 2nd &amp;ldquo;Pomegranate Seed Cup&amp;rdquo; Campus Dance Competition and Outstanding Dance Works Exhibition of Northwest University for Nationalities, every performer showed their charms on the stage with different dance styles. In this issue, we interviewed several performers, let&amp;rsquo;s listen to some of their experiences and stories in the dance in this exhibition!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map of Northwest University for Nationalities</title>
      <link>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/map-of-northwest-university-for-nationalities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/map-of-northwest-university-for-nationalities/</guid>
      <description>Northwest University for Nationalities Main Campus
Northwest University for Nationalities, Yuchong Campus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promotion｜The Fourth Gansu Dance &#34;Flying Apsaras Award&#34; Work--&#34;The Power of Faith</title>
      <link>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/promotion-the-fourth-gansu-dance-flying-apsaras-award-work-the-power-of-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 22:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miemiesun.github.io/newsite4/posts/promotion-the-fourth-gansu-dance-flying-apsaras-award-work-the-power-of-faith/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Power of Faith&amp;quot; is inspired by the deeds of Chen Hongjun, a representative of the outstanding soldiers in the new era and winner of the National &amp;ldquo;July 1 Medal&amp;rdquo;, and uses the realistic and unrealistic method to show that the soldiers in the border guards show that they do not forget the original heart and remember their mission under the harsh natural environment, highlighting the firm faith of the soldiers in the border guards that &amp;ldquo;a warrior is a boundary monument&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
